with and split infinitive is a
perfect example of that because split
infinitive is something that the idea
comes from Latin because in Latin
infinitives are one word so you
can't split them and you can't put an
adverb in the middle of in the
middle of the infinitive but English
isn't Latin it's a different language
and in English it seems fine to me
to say to boldly go to go boldly
seems okay as well boldly to go sounds
a bit weirder but kind of
what this is doing is and this is
coming back to stuckness what this is
doing is it's telling you that
you're not in the club and you're not
allowed
to write and you are in the club if
you can speak the language you can
write the language and other people
shouldn't be telling you that you
can't now you might do that and